<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<locale version="1.0"/>
<project>mod_SQLuserdb</project>
<language>eng</language>
<file>../modules/database/SQLuserdb.pike</file>

<str id="1">
<o>Database URL</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="2">
<o>This database to connect to as a database URL in the format &lt;br /&gt;&lt;tt&gt;driver://user name:password@host:port/database&lt;/tt&gt;.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="3">
<o>Passwords are crypted</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="4">
<o>If set, passwords are stored encrypted with the Unix &lt;i&gt;crypt&lt;/i&gt; funtion. If not, passwords are stored in clear text. </o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="5">
<o>Table</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="6">
<o>This is the table that contains the data. It must contain the columns &lt;i&gt;username&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;passwd&lt;/i&gt; and can contain the optional columns &lt;i&gt;uid&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;gid&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;gecos&lt;/i&gt; (the full name of the user), &lt;i&gt;homedir&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;shell&lt;/i&gt;. </o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="7">
<o>Disable user list</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="8">
<o>If this is turned on, it won't be possible to get a listing of all users. Usually the &lt;i&gt;User file system&lt;/i&gt; module makes it possible to list all users on the system. If you have a large number of users this can take a lot of resourses.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="9">
<o>Cache entries</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="10">
<o>If set, the module will cache database entries. Without this cache the module might well needs to make a database query per access. This option is therefore highly recommended. The drawback is changes to the database will not show up immediately.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="11">
<o>Close the database if not used</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="12">
<o>This option closes the database connection upon to long inactivity. Saves resourses for sites that are not used very frequently.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="13">
<o>Database close timeout</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="14">
<o>The inactivity time, in seconds, before the database connection is closed.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="15">
<o>Defaults: User ID</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="16">
<o>This is the uid that will be returned if a uid field is not present in the database table.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="17">
<o>Defaults: Group ID</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="18">
<o>This is the gid that will be returned is a gid field is not present in the database table.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="19">
<o>Defaults: Gecos</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="20">
<o>This is the gecos that will be returned if a gecos field is not present in the database table.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="21">
<o>Defaults: Home directory</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="22">
<o>This is the home directory that will be returned if a &lt;i&gt;homedir&lt;/i&gt; field is not present in the database table.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="23">
<o>Defaults: Login shell</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="24">
<o>This is the login shell that will be returned if a &lt;i&gt;shell&lt;/i&gt; field is not present in the database table.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="25">
<o>SQL user database</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="26">
<o>This module implements user authentication via a SQL server.
&lt;p&gt;For setup instruction, see the comments at the beginning of the module code.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;copy; 1997 Francesco Chemolli, distributed freely under GPL license.</o>
<t></t>
</str>
