<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<locale version="1.0"/>
<project>mod_userfs</project>
<language>eng</language>
<file>../modules/filesystems/userfs.pike</file>

<str id="1">
<o>File systems: User file system</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="2">
<o>A file system that gives access to files in the users' home
directories.  The users and home directories are found through the
current authentication module. The files from the home directories are
mounted either in the virtual file system of the site or as sites of
their own. So on one server the user Anne's files might be mounted on
&lt;tt&gt;http://domain.com/home/anne/&lt;/tt&gt; while another server might give
Anne a web site of her own at &lt;tt&gt;http://anne.domain.com/&lt;/tt&gt;.
</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="3">
<o>Search path</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="4">
<o>Password users only</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="5">
<o>Mount only home directories for users with valid passwords.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="6">
<o>Enable userlisting</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="7">
<o>If set a listing of all users will be shown when you access the mount point.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="8">
<o>Banish list</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="9">
<o>This is a list of users who's home directories will not be mounted.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="10">
<o>Only owned files</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="11">
<o>If set, only files actually owned by the user will be sent from her home directory. This prohibits users from making confidental files available by symlinking to them. On the other hand it also makes it harder for user to cooperate on projects.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="12">
<o>Virtual user hosting</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="13">
<o>If set, each user will get her own site. You access the user's with &lt;br&gt;&lt;tt&gt;http://&amp;lt;user&amp;gt;.domain.com/&amp;lt;mountpoint&amp;gt;&lt;/tt&gt; &lt;br&gt;instead of &lt;br&gt;&lt;tt&gt;http://domain.com/&amp;lt;mountpoint&amp;gt;&amp;lt;user&amp;gt;&lt;/tt&gt;. &lt;p&gt;This means that you normally set the mount point to '/'. &lt;p&gt;You need to set up CNAME entries in DNS for all users, or a regexp CNAME that matches all users, to get this to work.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="14">
<o>Run user scripts as the owner of the script</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="15">
<o>If set, users' CGI and Pike scripts will be run as the user whos home directory the file was found in. This only works if the  server was started as root.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="16">
<o>Public directory</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="17">
<o>This is the directory in the home directory of the users which contains the files that will be shown on the web. If the module is mounted on &lt;tt&gt;/home/&lt;/tt&gt;, the file &lt;tt&gt;/home/anne/test.html&lt;/tt&gt; is accessed and the home direcory of Anne is &lt;tt&gt;/export/users/anne/&lt;/tt&gt; the module will fetch the file &lt;tt&gt;/export/users/anne/&amp;lt;Public dir&amp;gt;/test.html&lt;/tt&gt;.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="18">
<o>Look in users homedir</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="19">
<o>If set, the module will look for the files in the user's home directory, according to the &lt;i&gt;Public directory&lt;/i&gt; variable. Otherwise the files are fetched from a directory with the same name as the user in the directory configured in the &lt;i&gt;Search path&lt;/i&gt; variable.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="20">
<o>You need at least one user database module in this virtual server to resolve your users' homedirectories.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="21">
<o>Add system user database module to server</o>
<t></t>
</str>
