<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<locale version="1.0"/>
<project>admin_tasks</project>
<language>deu</language>
<file>../config_interface/actions/cachestatus.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/change_version.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/connections.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/debug_info.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/debug_summary.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/feature_list.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/flush.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/ftpstatus.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/generate_rsa.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/licensestatus.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/listfonts.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/locks.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/make_rsa_csr.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/make_selfsigned_dsa.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/make_selfsigned_rsa.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/make_site_template.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/openfiles.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/patcher.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/pike_profiling.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/proc.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/reloadconfigurations.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/request_profiling.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/resolv.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/restart.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/ssl_common.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/tablist.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/threads.pike</file>
<file>../config_interface/actions/upload_license.pike</file>

<str id="1">
<o>Pike memory usage information</o>
<t>Informationen zur Speicherauslastung von Pike</t>
</str>

<str id="2">
<changed from="Show some information about how pike is using the memory it has allocated. Mostly useful for developers."/>
<o>Show some information about how Pike is using the memory it has allocated. Mostly useful for developers.</o>
<t>Zeigt einige Informationen, wie Pike den Speicher belegt.  Hauptsächlich sinnvoll für Entwickler.</t>
</str>

<str id="3">
<o>Type</o>
<t>Typ</t>
</str>

<str id="4">
<o>Number</o>
<t>Anzahl</t>
</str>

<str id="5">
<o>Change</o>
<t>Geändert</t>
</str>

<str id="6">
<o>Pike module list</o>
<t>Pike Modulliste</t>
</str>

<str id="7">
<o>Show information about which features and modules are available in the Pike this Roxen is using.</o>
<t>Zeigt Informationen über die Features und Module, die in der Pike-Version dieses Roxen verfügbar sind.</t>
</str>

<str id="238">
<o>Features</o>
<t>Features</t>
</str>

<str id="8">
<o>Flush caches</o>
<t>Caches leeren</t>
</str>

<str id="9">
<o>Flush all memory caches.</o>
<t>Alle Speicher-Caches leeren.</t>
</str>

<str id="232">
<o>All memory caches have been flushed.</o>
<t>Alle Speicher-Caches wurden geleert.</t>
</str>

<str id="10">
<o>List fonts</o>
<t>Schriftarten anzeigen</t>
</str>

<str id="11">
<o>List all available fonts</o>
<t>Alle zur Verfügung stehenden Schriftarten anzeigen.</t>
</str>

<str id="dH">
<o>Not available.</o>
<t>Nicht verfügbar.</t>
</str>

<str id="dI">
<o>All available fonts</o>
<t>Alle verfügbaren Schriftarten.</t>
</str>

<str id="236">
<o>Example text</o>
<t>Beispiel-Text</t>
</str>

<str id="237">
<o>Jackdaws love my big sphinx of quartz.</o>
<t>
schmerz bis qual folgt jeder unexakten motivtypwahl.
</t>
</str>

<str id="280">
<o>Module lock status</o>
<t>Modul-Lock-Status</t>
</str>

<str id="281">
<o>Shows various information about the module thread locks in Roxen.</o>
<t>Zeigt verschiedene Informationen über die Modul-Threads Locks an. </t>
</str>

<str id="12">
<o>Unknown module</o>
<t>Unbekanntes Modul</t>
</str>

<str id="13">
<o>Module lock status : Accesses to all modules</o>
<t>Modul-Lock-Status : Zugriff auf alle Module</t>
</str>

<str id="14">
<o>Locked means that the access was done using a serializing lock since the module was not thread-safe, unlocked means that there was no need for a lock.</o>
<t>Gesperrt bedeutet, dass der Zugriff durch Benutzung eines seriellen Locks erfolgte, da das Modul nicht thread-sicher ist.  Nicht gespeert bedeutet, dass es keine Notwendigkeit für ein solches Lock gab.</t>
</str>

<str id="15">
<o>Locked accesses to a single module can inflict quite a severe performance degradation of the whole server, since a locked module will act as a bottleneck, blocking access for all other threads that want to access that module.</o>
<t>Gesperrte Zugriffe auf ein einzelnen Modul können bemerkbare Auswirkungen auf die Performanz des gesamten Servers haben, da ein gesperrtes Modul als Flaschenhals agiert und Zugriffe von anderen Threads auf dieses Modul blockiert.</t>
</str>

<str id="17">
<o>Module</o>
<t>Modul</t>
</str>

<str id="18">
<o>File</o>
<t>Datei</t>
</str>

<str id="19">
<o>Locked</o>
<t>Gesperrt</t>
</str>

<str id="20">
<o>Unlocked</o>
<t>Nicht gesperrt</t>
</str>

<str id="21">
<o>Open files</o>
<t>Offene Dateien</t>
</str>

<str id="22">
<o>Show a list of all open files and network connections.</o>
<t>Zeigt eine Liste aller offener Dateien und Netzwerkverbindungen.</t>
</str>

<str id="23">
<o>Active filedescriptors</o>
<t>Aktive Dateideskriptoren</t>
</str>

<str id="24">
<o>Reload configurations from disk</o>
<t>Konfiguration von Festplatte neu laden</t>
</str>

<str id="25">
<o>Force a reload of all configuration information from the configuration files.</o>
<t>Neuladen sämtlicher Konfigurationen aus den Konfigurations-Dateien erzwingen.</t>
</str>

<str id="26">
<o>All configurations reloaded from disk.</o>
<t>Alle Konfigurationen wurden von Festplatte neu geladen.</t>
</str>

<str id="27">
<o>Resolve path...</o>
<t>Pfad auflösen...</t>
</str>

<str id="28">
<o>Check which modules handles the path you enter in the form</o>
<t>Nachverfolgung, welche Module den eingegebenen Pfad behandeln</t>
</str>

<str id="29">
<o>URL</o>
<t>URL</t>
</str>

<str id="206">
<o>User</o>
<t>Benutzer</t>
</str>

<str id="30">
<o>Password</o>
<t>Passwort</t>
</str>

<str id="31">
<o>There is no configuration available that matches this URL.</o>
<t>Keine Konfiguration für diese URL gefunden.</t>
</str>

<str id="32">
<o>Resolving</o>
<t>Verfolge</t>
</str>

<str id="33">
<o>in</o>
<t>in</t>
</str>

<str id="34">
<o>Restart or shutdown</o>
<t>Neustart oder Anhalten</t>
</str>

<str id="197">
<o>Restart</o>
<t>Neustart</t>
</str>

<str id="233">
<o>Roxen will restart automatically.</o>
<t>Roxen startet automatisch neu.</t>
</str>

<str id="234">
<o>You might see the old process for a while in the process table when doing 'ps' or running 'top'. This is normal. Roxen waits for a while for all connections to finish, the process will go away after at most 15 minutes.</o>
<t>Möglicherweise sehen Sie den alten Prozess noch eine Weile in der Prozesstabelle ('ps' oder 'top').  Dies ist normal.  Roxen wartet eine Weile, bis alle Verbindungen beendet sind, der Prozess verschwindet nach maximal 15 Minuten.</t>
</str>

<str id="226">
<o>Permission denied</o>
<t>Erlaubnis verweigert</t>
</str>

<str id="198">
<o>Shutdown</o>
<t>Anhalten</t>
</str>

<str id="235">
<o>Roxen will &lt;b&gt;not&lt;/b&gt; restart automatically.</o>
<t>Roxen startet &lt;b&gt;nicht&lt;/b&gt; automatisch neu.</t>
</str>

<str id="35">
<o>Thread backtrace</o>
<t>Thread-Rückverfolgung</t>
</str>

<str id="36">
<o>Shows a backtrace (stack) for each and every thread in Roxen.</o>
<t>Zeigt einen Backtrace (Stack) für alle Threads im Roxen an.</t>
</str>

<str id="37">
<o>version</o>
<t>Version</t>
</str>

<str id="38">
<o>backend thread</o>
<t>Backend-Thread</t>
</str>

<str id="39">
<o>Thread</o>
<t>Thread</t>
</str>

<str id="16">
<o>This is only a problem if a significant percentage of the accesses are passed through non-threadsafe modules.</o>
<t>Dies ist nur problematisch, wenn ein signifikanter Anteil der Zugriffe durch nicht thread-sichere Module laufen.</t>
</str>

<str id="228">
<o>Status</o>
<t>Status</t>
</str>

<str id="229">
<o>Maintenance</o>
<t>Pflege</t>
</str>

<str id="230">
<o>SSL</o>
<t>SSL</t>
</str>

<str id="231">
<changed from="Debug information"/>
<o>Debug Information</o>
<t>Debug-Informationen</t>
</str>

<str id="49">
<o>Current FTP sessions</o>
<t>Aktuelle FTP-Sitzungen</t>
</str>

<str id="50">
<o>List all active FTP sessions and what files they are currently transferring.</o>
<t>Listet alle aktiven FTP-Sitzungen und welche Dateien gerade übertragen werden.</t>
</str>

<str id="51">
<o>anonymous</o>
<t>Anonym</t>
</str>

<str id="52">
<o>idle</o>
<t>untätig</t>
</str>

<str id="53">
<o>From</o>
<t>Von</t>
</str>

<str id="54">
<o>CWD</o>
<t>Arbeitsverzeichnis</t>
</str>

<str id="55">
<o>Action</o>
<t>Aktion</t>
</str>

<str id="56">
<o>Transferred</o>
<t>Übertragen</t>
</str>

<str id="57">
<o>There are currently no active FTP sessions.</o>
<t>Es gibt derzeit keine aktiven FTP-Sitzungen.</t>
</str>

<str id="58">
<o>Available font loaders</o>
<t>Verfügbare Schriftarten-Lader</t>
</str>

<str id="59">
<o>Cache status</o>
<t>Cache-Status</t>
</str>

<str id="60">
<o>Show information about the main memory cache in Roxen</o>
<t>Zeige Informationen über den Hauptspeicher-Cache in Roxen</t>
</str>

<str id="61">
<o>WebServer Memory Cache</o>
<t>WebServer Speicher-Cache</t>
</str>

<str id="62">
<o>Class</o>
<t>Klasse</t>
</str>

<str id="64">
<o>Size</o>
<t>Größe</t>
</str>

<str id="67">
<o>Hit rate</o>
<t>Treffer-Quote</t>
</str>

<str id="68">
<changed from="supportdb"/>
<o>Supports database</o>
<t>Support-DB</t>
</str>

<str id="69">
<o>Fonts</o>
<t>Schriftarten</t>
</str>

<str id="70">
<o>DNS</o>
<t>DNS</t>
</str>

<str id="71">
<o>Locale Cache</o>
<t>Localer Cache</t>
</str>

<str id="72">
<o>Used languages:</o>
<t>Benutzte Sprachen:</t>
</str>

<str id="73">
<o>Registered projects:</o>
<t>Registrierte Projekte:</t>
</str>

<str id="74">
<o>Loaded project files:</o>
<t>Geladene Projektdateien:</t>
</str>

<str id="75">
<o>Current cache size:</o>
<t>Aktuelle Cache-Größe:</t>
</str>

<str id="295">
<o>Entries</o>
<t>Einträge</t>
</str>

<str id="293">
<o>Hits</o>
<t>Zugriffe</t>
</str>

<str id="294">
<o>Misses</o>
<t>Fehlschläge</t>
</str>

<str id="63">
<o>Extended process status</o>
<t>Erweiterter Prozess-Status</t>
</str>

<str id="65">
<o>Shows detailed process status on Solaris 2.5 and later.</o>
<t>Zeigt detailierten Prozess-Status unter Solaris 2.5 und höher.</t>
</str>

<str id="66">
<o>shared</o>
<t>geteilt</t>
</str>

<str id="76">
<o>private</o>
<t>privat</t>
</str>

<str id="77">
<o>resident</o>
<t>resistent</t>
</str>

<str id="78">
<o>groups:</o>
<t>Gruppen:</t>
</str>

<str id="79">
<o>and</o>
<t>und</t>
</str>

<str id="80">
<o>Process Tree for %d</o>
<t>Prozessbam für %d</t>
</str>

<str id="81">
<o>Misc status for %d</o>
<t>Zusätzlicher Status für %d</t>
</str>

<str id="82">
<o>Memory Usage:</o>
<t>Speicher-Bedarf:</t>
</str>

<str id="83">
<o>Credentials:</o>
<t>Bescheinigungen:</t>
</str>

<str id="84">
<o>Current working directory:</o>
<t>Aktuelles Arbeitsverzeichnis:</t>
</str>

<str id="88">
<o>The other part should be submitted to a certificate authority, such as Thawte or VeriSign. The certificate authority will return the signed certificate that need to run a secure server.</o>
<t>Der andere Teil sollte an eine Certificate Authority, wie Thawte oder VeriSign, eingesendet werden. Diese Authority sendet das unterzeichnete Zertifikat zurück, das für den sicheren Server benötigt wird.</t>
</str>

<str id="89">
<o>The other part is used to create a certificate. You can create a certificate yourself; this is not the recommended way to use SSL, and browsers will complain about not recognizing the entity that has signed the key (i.e. you). But a self-signed certificate is a lot better than nothing.</o>
<t>Der andere Teil wird für die Erstellung eines Zertifikats gebraucht. Sie können ein Zertifikat selbst erstellen; dies ist nicht der empfohlene Weg, SSL zu benutzen, und Browser werden sich beschweren, dass sie das Zertifikat nicht anerkennen. Aber ein selbst-signiertes Zertifikat ist besser als keines und reicht zum testen.</t>
</str>

<str id="90">
<o>Keys smaller than %d bits are ridiculous.</o>
<t>Schlüssel kleiner als %d Bits sind lächerlich.</t>
</str>

<str id="91">
<o>Keys larger than %d bits would take too long to generate.</o>
<t>Schlüssel mit mehr als %d Bits brauchen zu lange in der Generierung.</t>
</str>

<str id="92">
<o>How large key do you want to generate?</o>
<t>Wie groß soll der zu generierende Schlüssel sein?</t>
</str>

<str id="93">
<o>The desired key size. This is a security parameter; larger keys gives better security, but it also makes connecting to the server a little slower.</o>
<t>Die benötigte Schlüsselgröße. Dies ist ein Sicherheitsparameter; größere Schlüssel geben eine höhere Sicherheit, aber verlangsamt auch die Verbindungen zum Server.</t>
</str>

<str id="94">
<o>Key size</o>
<t>Schlüsselgröße</t>
</str>

<str id="95">
<o>The largest key that is publicly known to have been broken was 155 decimal digits, or 512 bits large. This effort required approximately 8000 MIPS-years.&lt;p&gt;A key 1024 bits large should be secure enough for most applications, but of course you can you use an even larger key if you so wish.</o>
<t>Der größte Schlüssel, der bisher geknackt wurde, hatte 155 Dezimalstellen, oder 512 Bits. Dieser Aufwand erfordert in etwa 8000 MIPS-Jahre.&lt;p&amp;pt;Ein Schlüssel mit 1024 Bit ist sicher genug für die meisten Anwendungen, aber natürlich kann man diese Größe noch erhöhen.</t>
</str>

<str id="96">
<o>Key file</o>
<t>Schlüssel-Datei</t>
</str>

<str id="97">
<o>Where to store the file, may be relative to %s.</o>
<t>Wo soll die Datei abgelegt werden, relativ zu %s.</t>
</str>

<str id="98">
<o>A filename in the real filesystem, where the secret key should be stored. This is the filename you enter in the 'Key file'-field when you configure an SSL listen port.</o>
<t>Ein Dateiname im realen Dateisystem, in dem der geheime Schlüssel abgelegt werden soll. Dies ist der Dateiname in dem 'Schlüssel-Datei'-Feld, den man beim Konfigurieren eines SSL-Ports eingegeben hat.</t>
</str>

<str id="99">
<o>Your Distinguished Name?</o>
<t>Ihr Distinguished Name?</t>
</str>

<str id="100">
<o>Your X.501 Distinguished Name consists of a chain of attributes and values, where each link in the chain defines more precisely who you are. Which attributes are necessary or useful depends on what you will use the certificate for, and which Certificate Authority you use. This page lets you specify the most useful attributes. If you leave a field blank, that attribute will be omitted from your name.&lt;p&gt;
Although most browsers will accept 8 bit ISO 8859-1 characters in these fields, it can't be counted on. To be on the safe side, use only US-ASCII.</o>
<t>Ihr X.501 Distinguished Name besteht aus einer Reihe von Attributen und Werten, die genau beschreiben, wer Sie sind.</t>
</str>

<str id="101">
<o>Your country code</o>
<t>Ihr Ländercode.</t>
</str>

<str id="102">
<o>Your two-letter country code, for example GB (United Kingdom). This attribute is required.</o>
<t>Ihr zweistelliger Ländercode, z.B. DE (Deutschland). Dieses Attribut ist notwendig.</t>
</str>

<str id="103">
<o>State/Province</o>
<t>Staat/Bundesland</t>
</str>

<str id="104">
<o>The state where you are operating. VeriSign requires this attribute to be present for US and Canadian customers. Do not abbreviate.</o>
<t>Der Staat oder das Bundesland, in dem Sie ansässig sind. VeriSign verlangt die Existenz dieses Attributs bei Kunden aus den USA oder Kanada. Keine Abkürzungen verwenden.</t>
</str>

<str id="105">
<o>City/Locality</o>
<t>Stadt/Örtlichkeit</t>
</str>

<str id="106">
<o>The city or locality where you are registered. VeriSign requires that at least one of the locality and the state attributes are present. Do not abbreviate.</o>
<t>Die Stadt oder Örtlichkeit, wo Sie registriert sind. VeriSign verlangt das mindestens ein Wert angegeben wird. Keine Abkürzungen verwenden.</t>
</str>

<str id="107">
<o>Organization/Company</o>
<t>Organization/Firma</t>
</str>

<str id="108">
<o>The organization name under which you are registered with some national or regional authority.</o>
<t>Die Organisation, unter der Sie national oder regional registriert sind.</t>
</str>

<str id="109">
<o>Organizational unit</o>
<t>Organisationseinheit</t>
</str>

<str id="110">
<o>This attribute is optional, and there are no specific requirements on the value of this attribute.</o>
<t>Dieses Attribut ist optional, und es gibt keine besondere Notwendigkeit dieses Wertes.</t>
</str>

<str id="111">
<o>Common Name</o>
<t>Common Name</t>
</str>

<str id="112">
<o>This is the DNS name of your server (i.e. the host part of the URL).&lt;p&gt;Browsers will compare the URL they are connecting to with the Common Name in the server's certificate, and warn the user if they don't match.&lt;p&gt;Some Certificate Authorities allow wild cards in the Common Name. This means that you can have a certificate for &lt;tt&gt;*.roxen.com&lt;/tt&gt; which will match all servers at Roxen.Thawte allows wild card certificates, while VeriSign does not.</o>
<t>Dies ist der DNS-Name Ihres Servers (i.e. der Hostteil der URL).&lt;p&gt;Browser vergleichen die aktuelle URL mit dem Common Name im Server-Zertifikat und warnen den Benutzer, wenn diese Namen nicht übereinstimmen. Einige Zertifikate erlauben Wildcards im Common Name. D.h. Sie können ein Zertifikat für &lt;tt&gt;*.roxen.com&lt;/tt&gt; haben, das für alle Server gilt. Thawte erlaubt Wildcard-Zertifikate, VeriSign nicht.</t>
</str>

<str id="113">
<o>For how long should the certificate be valid?</o>
<t>Wie lange soll das Zertifikat gültig sein?</t>
</str>

<str id="114">
<o>Certificate lifetime, in days</o>
<t>Lebensdauer des Zertifikats, in Tagen</t>
</str>

<str id="115">
<o>A certificate includes a validity period. How many days, from now, do you want the certificate to be valid?</o>
<t>Ein Zertifikat enthält eine Gültigkeitsdauer.  Wie viele Tage, von nun an, soll das Zertifikat gültig sein?</t>
</str>

<str id="116">
<o>Save the request in a file:</o>
<t>Speichern des Requests in eine Datei:</t>
</str>

<str id="117">
<o>Filename</o>
<t>Dateiname</t>
</str>

<str id="118">
<o>Generate a new RSA key pair...</o>
<t>Generierung eines neuen RSA-Schlüsselpaares...</t>
</str>

<str id="119">
<o>Note that it is possible to have more than one certificate for the same key.</o>
<t>Anmerkung: Es ist möglich, mehr als ein Zertifikat für denselben Schlüssel zu haben.</t>
</str>

<str id="120">
<o>Wrote %d-bit key in %s</o>
<t>%d-Bit-Schlüssel in %s geschrieben</t>
</str>

<str id="121">
<o>Generate a Certificate Signing Request and an RSA key...</o>
<t>Generierung eines Certificate Signing Requests und eines RSA-Schlüssels...</t>
</str>

<str id="122">
<o>Certificate Attributes?</o>
<t>Zertifikat-Attribute?</t>
</str>

<str id="123">
<o>An X.509 certificate associates a Common Name with a public key. Some certificate authorities support "extended certificates", defined in PKCS#10. An extended certificate may contain other useful information associated with the name and the key. This information is signed by the CA, together with the X.509 certificate.</o>
<t>Ein X.509 Zertifikat verknüpft einen Common Name mit einem öffentlichen Schlüssel. Einige Certificate Authorities unterstützen "erweiterte Zertifikate", wie in PKCS#10 definiert. Ein erweitertes Zertifikat kann weitere nützliche Informationen zum Namen und Schlüssel enthalten. Diese Informationen werden von der CA signiert, zusammen mit dem X.509 Zertifikat.</t>
</str>

<str id="124">
<o>Email address</o>
<t>Email-Adresse</t>
</str>

<str id="125">
<o>An email address to be embedded in the certificate.</o>
<t>Eine Email-Adresse, die im Zertifikat eingebunden wird.</t>
</str>

<str id="126">
<o>CSR Attributes?</o>
<t>CSR-Attribute?</t>
</str>

<str id="127">
<o>At last, you can add attributes to the Certificate Signing Request, which are meant for the Certificate Authority and are not included in the issued Certificate.</o>
<t>Abschliessend können Sie Attribute zum Certificate Signing Request hinzufügen, die für die Certificate Authority gedacht sind und nicht in dem ausgestellten Zertifikat enthalten sind.</t>
</str>

<str id="128">
<o>Challenge Password</o>
<t>Challenge-Passwort</t>
</str>

<str id="129">
<o>This password could be used if you ever want to revoke your certificate. Of course, this depends on the policy of your Certificate Authority.</o>
<t>Dieses Password kann benötigt werden, falls Sie jemals Ihr Zertifikat widerrufen wollen.  Dies hängt von der Policy Ihrer Certificate Authority ab.</t>
</str>

<str id="130">
<o>This is your Certificate Signing Request.</o>
<t>Dies ist Ihr Certificate Signing Request.</t>
</str>

<str id="131">
<o>Wrote %d bytes to %s.</o>
<t>%d Bytes nach %s geschrieben.</t>
</str>

<str id="132">
<o>Generate an RSA key and a Self Signed Certificate...</o>
<t>Generierung eines RSA-Schlüssels und eines selbst-signierten Zertifikats...</t>
</str>

<str id="133">
<o>This is your Certificate.</o>
<t>Dies ist Ihr Zertifikat.</t>
</str>

<str id="134">
<o>Generate an DSA key and a Self Signed Certificate...</o>
<t>Generierung eines DSA-Schlüssels und eines selbst-signierten Zertifikats...</t>
</str>

<str id="135">
<o>Invalid key size.</o>
<t>Ungültige Schlüssel-Größe.</t>
</str>

<str id="40">
<o>In order to use the SSL on your server, you first have to create a random key pair. One part of the key is kept secret. </o>
<t>Um SSL auf Ihren Server zu benutzen, müssen Sie zunöchst ein zufälliges Schlüsselpaar erzeugen. Ein Teil des Schlüssels wird privat verwahrt.</t>
</str>

<str id="42">
<o>If you have more than one Roxen version installed
in the same location, you can use this action to
change the currently running version.</o>
<t>Wenn mehr als eine Roxen-Version im gleichen Verzeichnis installiert
ist, kann diese Auswahl die aktuell laufende Version wechseln.</t>
</str>

<str id="43">
<o>1 month</o>
<t>1 Monat</t>
</str>

<str id="44">
<o>%d months</o>
<t>%d Monate</t>
</str>

<str id="45">
<o>%d days</o>
<t>%d Tage</t>
</str>

<str id="46">
<o>Change Roxen version</o>
<t>Roxen-Version wechseln</t>
</str>

<str id="47">
<changed from="Shutting down and changing roxen version"/>
<o>Shutting down and changing Roxen version</o>
<t>Herunterfahren und Roxen-Version ändern</t>
</str>

<str id="48">
<o>Version</o>
<t>Version</t>
</str>

<str id="85">
<o>Release date</o>
<t>Freigabe-Datum</t>
</str>

<str id="86">
<o>Age</o>
<t>Alter</t>
</str>

<str id="136">
<o>Directory</o>
<t>Verzeichnis</t>
</str>

<str id="137">
<changed from="If you change to one these roxen versions, you will not be able to change back from the administration interface, you will instead have to edit the file %O manually, shutdown the server, and execute %O again"/>
<o>If you change to one these Roxen versions, you will not be able to change back from the administration interface, you will instead have to edit the file %O manually, shutdown the server, and execute %O again</o>
<t>Wenn Sie auf eine dieser Roxen-Versionen wechseln, ist es nicht mehr möglich, aus diesem Adminstrations-Interface zurückzuwechseln.  Sie müssen stattdessen die Datei %O bearbeiten, den Server anhalten und %O erneut ausführen</t>
</str>

<str id="138">
<o>Change version</o>
<t>Version wechseln</t>
</str>

<str id="87">
<o>Non-garbing Memory Cache</o>
<t>Speicher-Cache (Ohne Garbage Collection)</t>
</str>

<str id="139">
<o>one day</o>
<t>ein Tag</t>
</str>

<str id="140">
<o>Unavailable features</o>
<t>Nicht verfügbare Features</t>
</str>

<str id="141">
<o>Source</o>
<t>Quelle</t>
</str>

<str id="142">
<o>Program</o>
<t>Programm</t>
</str>

<str id="143">
<o>Clones</o>
<t>Clones</t>
</str>

<str id="144">
<o>Create site template</o>
<t>Site-Template erstellen</t>
</str>

<str id="145">
<o>Create a site template from a site configuration</o>
<t>Site-Template aus anderer Site-Konfiguration erstellen</t>
</str>

<str id="146">
<o>Coundn't find configuration</o>
<t>Konfiguration konnte nicht gefunden werden</t>
</str>

<str id="147">
<o>Select configuration to base the template on.</o>
<t>Konfiguration als Grundlage für Template auswählen.</t>
</str>

<str id="148">
<o>Selected configuration</o>
<t>Ausgewählte Konfigurationen</t>
</str>

<str id="149">
<o>Coundn't create directory</o>
<t>Verzeichnis konnte nicht erstellt werden</t>
</str>

<str id="150">
<o>Failed to create template file</o>
<t>Fehler beim Erstellen der Template-Datei</t>
</str>

<str id="151">
<o>Failed to write template file</o>
<t>Fehler beim Schreiben der Template-Datei</t>
</str>

<str id="152">
<o>Site template created successfully.</o>
<t>Site-Template erfolgreich erstellt.</t>
</str>

<str id="154">
<o>Note that you will have to start the new server manually because you may have to answer a few questions for the new environment file.</o>
<t>Hinweis: Der neue Server muss manuell gestartet werden, weil möglicherweise eine Fragen zur neuen Umgebung beantwortet werden müssen</t>
</str>

<str id="155">
<o>Failed to write CSR to %s.</o>
<t>Schreiben des CSR nach %s fehlgeschlagen.</t>
</str>

<str id="156">
<changed from="Active connection"/>
<o>Active connections</o>
<t>Aktive Verbindungen</t>
</str>

<str id="157">
<changed from="All currently active connection"/>
<o>All currently active connections</o>
<t>Alle derzeit aktiven Verbindungen</t>
</str>

<str id="158">
<o>Time</o>
<t>Zeit</t>
</str>

<str id="159">
<o>Sent (Mib)</o>
<t>Versendet (Mib)</t>
</str>

<str id="160">
<o>Kibyte/s</o>
<t>Kibyte/s</t>
</str>

<str id="161">
<o>Total bandwidth</o>
<t>Gesamte Bandbreite</t>
</str>

<str id="163">
<changed from="Debug Summary"/>
<o>Debug summary</o>
<t>Debug-Zusammenfassung</t>
</str>

<str id="164">
<o>Shows a text file containing a configuration summary, suitable for support purposes.</o>
<t>Anzeige einer Textdatei mit Zusammenfassung der Konfiguration, für Support-Zwecke.</t>
</str>

<str id="165">
<o>License status</o>
<t>Lizenz-Status</t>
</str>

<str id="166">
<changed from="Show information about the installed licenses and there usage."/>
<o>Show information about the installed licenses and their usage.</o>
<t>Zeigt Informationen über die installierten Lizenzen und deren Verwendung</t>
</str>

<str id="168">
<changed from="Upload a new roxen license file."/>
<o>Upload a new Roxen license file.</o>
<t>Eine neue Roxen Lizenzdatei einspielen.</t>
</str>

<str id="169">
<new/>
<o>The garbage collector freed %d of %d things (%d%%).</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="170">
<new/>
<o>%d seconds since last garbage collection, %d%% of the interval is consumed.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="172">
<new/>
<o>Garbage collector status</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="173">
<new/>
<o>Internal inconsistency</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="174">
<new/>
<o>Object(s) missing in object link list.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="175">
<new/>
<o>Warning</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="176">
<new/>
<o>Number of objects changed during object walkthrough (probably due to automatic gc call) - the list below is not complete.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="177">
<new/>
<o>The object walkthrough visited %d of %d objects - the list below is not accurate.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="178">
<new/>
<o>Total</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="179">
<new/>
<o>Canonic URL: </o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="180">
<new/>
<o>Upload license...</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="41">
<new/>
<o>Download</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="153">
<new/>
<o>Download Debug Log</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="162">
<new/>
<o>Pike profiling information</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="167">
<new/>
<o>Show some information about how much time has been spent in various functions. Mostly useful for developers.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="181">
<new/>
<o>Request profiling information</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="182">
<new/>
<o>Show some information about how how much time has been spent in requests. Mostly useful for developers.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="183">
<new/>
<o>All times are in microseconds.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="184">
<new/>
<o>NOTE: This information is only available if the server has been stared with &lt;tt&gt;-DPROFILE&lt;/tt&gt;.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="185">
<new/>
<o>This information is only available if the pike binary has been compiled with &lt;tt&gt;--with-profiling&lt;/tt&gt;.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="186">
<new/>
<o>Refresh</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="187">
<new/>
<o>Reset</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="188">
<new/>
<o>Unable to parse URL.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="296">
<new/>
<o>HTTP auth</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="297">
<new/>
<o>Form variables</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="325">
<new/>
<o>HTTP Cookies</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="326">
<new/>
<o>Patch management</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="327">
<new/>
<o>Show information about the available patches and their status.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="328">
<new/>
<o>Installed by:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="329">
<new/>
<o>Installed:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="330">
<new/>
<o>Unknown</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="331">
<new/>
<o>Uninstalled:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="332">
<new/>
<o>Uninstalled by:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="333">
<new/>
<o>Description:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="334">
<new/>
<o>Originator:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="335">
<new/>
<o>Yes</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="336">
<new/>
<o>No</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="337">
<new/>
<o>Flags:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="338">
<new/>
<o>Platforms:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="339">
<new/>
<o>All platforms</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="340">
<new/>
<o>Platform:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="341">
<new/>
<o>Platform</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="342">
<new/>
<o>Target version:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="343">
<new/>
<o>All versions</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="344">
<new/>
<o>installed</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="345">
<new/>
<o>imported</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="346">
<new/>
<o>unavailable</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="347">
<new/>
<o>Dependencies:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="348">
<new/>
<o>None</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="349">
<new/>
<o>New file:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="350">
<new/>
<o>New files:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="351">
<new/>
<o>Replaced file:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="352">
<new/>
<o>Replaced files:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="353">
<new/>
<o>Deleted file:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="354">
<new/>
<o>Deleted files:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="355">
<new/>
<o>Patched file:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="356">
<new/>
<o>Patched files:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="357">
<new/>
<o>No patches found</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="358">
<new/>
<o>Uninstall selected patches</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="359">
<new/>
<o>Install selected patches</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="360">
<new/>
<o>Importing</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="361">
<new/>
<o>Patch successfully imported.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="362">
<new/>
<o>Could not import patch.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="363">
<new/>
<o>Uninstalling</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="364">
<new/>
<o>Done!</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="365">
<new/>
<o>Failed to uninstall the patch. See the log below for details</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="366">
<new/>
<o>Patch uninstalled successfully. See the log below for details</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="367">
<new/>
<o>%d out of %d patches sucessfully uninstalled. See the log below for details.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="368">
<new/>
<o>The server needs to be restarted.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="369">
<new/>
<o>Would you like to do  that now?</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="370">
<new/>
<o>Installing</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="371">
<new/>
<o>Failed to install the patch. See the log below for details</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="372">
<new/>
<o>Patch successfully installed. See the log below for details</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="373">
<new/>
<o>Import a New Patch</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="374">
<new/>
<o>Select local file to upload:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="375">
<new/>
<o>Imported Patches</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="376">
<new/>
<o>These are patches that are not currently installed; they are imported but not applied. It should be safe to remove them from disk. They can be found in local/patches/.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="377">
<new/>
<o>Click on a patch for more information.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="378">
<new/>
<o>Installed Patches</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="379">
<new/>
<o>Click on a Patch for more information.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="380">
<new/>
<o>Configure cache settings</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="381">
<new/>
<o>The configured maximum size %s is divided dynamically between the
cache managers based on the usage for the last half hour. If the
caches are not full then all free space is assigned to each one of
them. They will shrink to the configured maximum size as they fill up.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="382">
<new/>
<o>Cache manager</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="383">
<new/>
<o>Size limit</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="384">
<new/>
<o>Input rate</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="385">
<new/>
<o>Cost HR</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="386">
<new/>
<o>Cache manager: </o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="387">
<new/>
<o>Lookups</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="388">
<new/>
<o>Size/entry</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="389">
<new/>
<o>Byte HR</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="390">
<new/>
<o>Create cost</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="391">
<new/>
<o>Cost/entry</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="392">
<new/>
<o>&lt;i&gt;Cost HR&lt;/i&gt; is the cost hit rate, i.e. every hit and miss is
weighted with the cost for each entry according to the cost metric of
the cache manager. Note that it uses the approximation that every
cache miss is followed by the addition of a new cache entry.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="393">
<new/>
<o>Garbage Collector</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="394">
<new/>
<o>The garbage collector has not run yet.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="395">
<new/>
<o>%d seconds since the last garbage collection. The following statistics are over approximately the last hour.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="396">
<new/>
<o>Time spent in the garbage collector:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="397">
<new/>
<o>Size of garbage collected entries:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="398">
<new/>
<o>stale</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="399">
<new/>
<o>timed out</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="400">
<new/>
<o>Garbage collection ratio:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="401">
<new/>
<o>Note that the garbage collector referred to here is not the same as
the one for the &lt;a
href='/actions/?action=cachestatus.pike&amp;class=status'&gt;Roxen memory
cache&lt;/a&gt;. This is the low-level garbage collector used internally by
the Pike interpreter.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="402">
<new/>
<o>Cache</o>
<t></t>
</str>
