<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<locale version="1.0"/>
<project>roxen_config</project>
<language>deu</language>
<dumped>966020809</dumped>

<str id="1">
<new/>
<o>No virtual servers enabled</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="2">
<new/>
<o>Sent data</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="3">
<new/>
<o>sec</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="4">
<new/>
<o>Sent headers</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="5">
<new/>
<o>Number of requests</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="6">
<new/>
<o>min</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="7">
<new/>
<o>Received data</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="8">
<new/>
<o>FTP users (total)</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="9">
<new/>
<o>FTP users (now)</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="10">
<o>FTP statistics</o>
<t>FTP-Statistik</t>
</str>

<str id="11">
<new/>
<o>Reloaded %s.
</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="12">
<new/>
<o>Priority</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="13">
<o>The priority of the module. 9 is highest and 0 is lowest. Modules with the same priority can be assumed to be called in random order</o>
<t>Modul Priorität. 9 höchste, 0 niedrigste. Module mit gleicher Priorität werden in zufälliger Reihenfolge aufgerufen.</t>
</str>

<str id="14">
<new/>
<o>Security: Realm</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="15">
<o>The realm to use when requesting password from the client. Usually used as an informative message to the user.</o>
<t>Bereichsname, der benutzt werden soll, wenn vom Webbrowser ein Passwort angefordert werden soll. Wird üblicherweise als informativer Hinweis für den Benutzer verwendet.</t>
</str>

<str id="16">
<new/>
<o>Security: Patterns</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="17">
<o>This is the 'security level=value' list.&lt;br /&gt;Each security level can be any or more from this list:&lt;hr noshade="noshade" /&gt;allow ip=&lt;i&gt;IP&lt;/i&gt;/&lt;i&gt;bits&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;allow ip=&lt;i&gt;IP&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;i&gt;mask&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;allow ip=&lt;i&gt;pattern&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;allow user=&lt;i&gt;username&lt;/i&gt;,...&lt;br /&gt;deny ip=&lt;i&gt;IP&lt;/i&gt;/&lt;i&gt;bits&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;deny ip=&lt;i&gt;IP&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;i&gt;mask&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;deny ip=&lt;i&gt;pattern&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr noshade="noshade" /&gt;In patterns: * matches one or more characters, and ? matches one character.&lt;p&gt;In username: 'any' stands for any valid account (from .htaccess or an auth module. The default (used when _no_ entries are present) is 'allow ip=*', allowing everyone to access the module.&lt;/p&gt;</o>
<t>Dies ist die Liste der Sicherheitsmuster.&lt;p&gt;Jede Sicherheitsebene kann aus einem oder mehr der folgenden Einträgen bestehen: &lt;hr noshade&gt;allow ip=&lt;i&gt;IP-Adresse&lt;/i&gt;/&lt;i&gt;Bits&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;allow ip=&lt;i&gt;IP-Adresse&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;i&gt;Netzmaske&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;allow ip=&lt;i&gt;Muster&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;allow user=&lt;i&gt;Benutzername&lt;/i&gt;,...&lt;br&gt;deny ip=&lt;i&gt;IP-Adresse&lt;/i&gt;/&lt;i&gt;Bits&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;deny ip=&lt;i&gt;IP-nummer&lt;/i&gt;:&lt;i&gt;Netzmaske&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;deny ip=&lt;i&gt;Muster&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr noshade&gt;Bei den Mustern trifft '*' auf ein oder mehrere Zeichen zu, '?' auf genau ein Zeichen.&lt;p&gt; Bei den Benutzernamen steht 'any' für jeden gültigen Benutzernamen (aus einer .htaccess-Datei oder jedem anderen Auth-Modul)  Der Standard-Wert (wenn keine Eingaben gemacht wurden), ist 'allow ip=*', d.h. jeder darf auf das Modul zugreifen.</t>
</str>

<str id="18">
<new/>
<o>Security: Security level</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="19">
<o>The modules security level is used to determine if a  request should be handled by the module.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Security level vs Trust level&lt;/h2&gt; Each module has a configurable &lt;i&gt;security level&lt;/i&gt;. Each request has an assigned trust level. Higher &lt;i&gt;trust levels&lt;/i&gt; grants access to modules with higher &lt;i&gt;security levels&lt;/i&gt;.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Definitions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;A requests initial Trust level is infinitely high.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; A request will only be handled by a module if its     &lt;i&gt;trust level&lt;/i&gt; is higher or equal to the     &lt;i&gt;security level&lt;/i&gt; of the module.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; Each time the request is handled by a module the     &lt;i&gt;trust level&lt;/i&gt; of the module will be set to the      lower of its &lt;i&gt;trust level&lt;/i&gt; and the modules     &lt;i&gt;security level&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt; Modules:&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;  User filesystem, &lt;i&gt;security level&lt;/i&gt; 1&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;  Filesystem module, &lt;i&gt;security level&lt;/i&gt; 3&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;  CGI module, &lt;i&gt;security level&lt;/i&gt; 2&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A request handled by "User filesystem" is assigned a &lt;i&gt;trust level&lt;/i&gt; of one after the &lt;i&gt;security level&lt;/i&gt; of that module. That request can then not be handled by the "CGI module" since that module has a higher &lt;i&gt;security level&lt;/i&gt; than the requests trust level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, a request handled by the the "Filsystem module" could later be handled by the "CGI module".&lt;/p&gt;</o>
<t>Die Sicherheitsebene des Moduls wird verwendet, wenn ein Request vom Modul behandelt werden soll.\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sicherheitsebene vs Vertrauensebene&lt;/h2&gt; Jedes Modul hat eine konfigurierbare &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt;.Jeder Request hat eine zugewiesene Vertrauensebene. Höhere &lt;i&gt;Vertrauensebeben&lt;/i&gt; erlauben Zugriff zu Modulen mir höherer &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt;.\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Definitionen&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Die ursprüngliche Vertrauensebene eines Requests      ist unendlich hoch. &lt;li&gt; Ein Request wird nur von einem Modul behandelt, wenn      seine &lt;i&gt;Vertrauensebene&lt;/i&gt; mindestens so hoch ist,      wie die &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt; des Moduls. &lt;li&gt; Jedes Mal wenn ein Request von einem Modul       behandelt wird, wird die &lt;i&gt;Vertrauensebene&lt;/i&gt;      des Requests auf den jeweils niedrigeren Wert      von der &lt;i&gt;Vertrauensebene&lt;/i&gt; des Requests und der     &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt; des Moduls, gesetzt. &lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Beispiel&lt;/h2&gt; Module:&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;  User filesystem, &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt; 1 &lt;li&gt;  Filesystem module, &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt; 3 &lt;li&gt;  CGI module, &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt; 2 &lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;Ein Request der vom \"User filesystem\" behandelt wird bekommt eine &lt;i&gt;Vertrauensebene&lt;/i&gt; die der &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt; des Moduls entspricht. Der Request kann dann nicht mehr vom \"CGI module\
                   "behandelt werden, da dieses eine höhere &lt;i&gt;Sicherheitsebene&lt;/i&gt; hat als die Vertrauensebene des Requests.\n&lt;p&gt;Ein Request der vom \"Filsystem module\" behandelt wurde kann andererseits später vom \"CGI module\
                   "behandelt werden.</t>
</str>

<str id="20">
<new/>
<o>Default site</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="21">
<new/>
<o>If true, this site will be selected in preference of other sites when virtual hosting is used and no host header is supplied, or the supplied host header does not match the address of any of the other servers.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="22">
<new/>
<o>Virtual server comment</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="23">
<o>This text will be visible in the administration interface, it can be quite useful to use as a memory helper.</o>
<t>Ein Kommentar, der im Konfigurations-Interface sichtbar ist und als Dokumentation nützlich ist.</t>
</str>

<str id="24">
<new/>
<o>Virtual server name</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="25">
<o>This is the name that will be used in the configuration interface. If this is left empty, the actual name of the virtual server will be used.</o>
<t>Dies ist der Name, der im Konfigurations-Interface für den
  virtuellen Server benutzt wird.  Wird dieses Feld leer gelassen,
  wird der eigentliche Name des virtuellen Servers benutzt.</t>
</str>

<str id="26">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Format</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="27">
<o>What format to use for logging. The syntax is:
&lt;pre&gt;response-code or *: Log format for that response code

Log format is normal characters, or one or more of the variables below:

\n \t \r       -- As in C, newline, tab and linefeed
$char(int)     -- Insert the (1 byte) character specified by the integer.
$wchar(int)    -- Insert the (2 byte) word specified by the integer.
$int(int)      -- Insert the (4 byte) word specified by the integer.
$^             -- Supress newline at the end of the logentry
$host          -- The remote host name, or ip number.
$ip_number     -- The remote ip number.
$bin-ip_number -- The remote host id as a binary integer number.

$cern_date     -- Cern Common Log file format date.
$bin-date      -- Time, but as an 32 bit integer in network byteorder

$method        -- Request method
$resource      -- Resource identifier
$full_resource -- Full requested resource, including any query fields
$protocol      -- The protocol used (normally HTTP/1.0)
$response      -- The response code sent
$bin-response  -- The response code sent as a binary short number
$length        -- The length of the data section of the reply
$bin-length    -- Same, but as an 32 bit integer in network byteorder
$request-time  -- The time the request took (seconds)
$referer       -- the header 'referer' from the request, or '-'.
$user_agent    -- the header 'User-Agent' from the request, or '-'.

$user          -- the name of the auth user used, if any
$user_id       -- A unique user ID, if cookies are supported,
                  by the client, otherwise '0'
&lt;/pre&gt;</o>
<t>Welches Format soll für die Logfiles benutzt werden.
&lt;pre&gt;
Antwort-Code oder *: Loggingformat für diesen Antwort-Code (z.B 404)

Das Loggingformat ist normaler Text, in den folgende
Variabeln eingesetzt werden können.

\\n \\t \\r    -- Newline, Tab oder Linefeed-Zeichen (wie in C)
$char(int)     -- Fügt das 8Bit-Zeichen ein, das dem Integerwert entspricht.
$wchar(int)    -- Fügt das 16Bit-Zeichen ein, das dem Integerwert entspricht.
$int(int)      -- Fügt das 32Bit-Word ein, das dem Integerwert entspricht.
$^             -- Unterdrückt das Newline-Zeichen am Ende des Eintrages.
$host          -- Hostname oder IP-Adresse des Webbrowsers.
$ip_number     -- IP-Adresse des Webbrowsers.
$bin-ip_number -- IP-Adresse des Webbrowsers in 32Bit-Dezimaldarstellung.
$cern_date     -- Uhrzeit und Datum im CERN-Format.
$bin-date      -- Zeit als 32Bit-Integer-Darstellung (Sekunden seit 1.1.1970).
$method        -- Anfrage-Methode (GET, POST, usw.)
$resource      -- Angeforderte Datei.
$protocol      -- Verwendetes Protokoll (normalerweise HTTP/1.0 oder HTTP/1.1)
$response      -- Der verschichte Antwort-Code
$bin-response  -- Der verschickte Antwort-Code in 32Bit-Dezimaldarstellung
$length        -- Die Größe der verschickten Daten
$bin-length    -- Die Größe der verschickten Daten in 32Bit-Dezimaldarstellung
$request-time  -- Verstrichene Zeit in Sekunden, die die Anfrage benötigt hat
$referer       -- Die 'referer'-Information aus der Anfrage, oder '-'
$user_agent    -- Die 'user-agent'-Information aus der Anfrage, oder '-'
$user          -- Der Name des angemeldeten Benutzers, sofern vorhanden
$user_id       -- Die eindeutige Benutzerkennung, sofern Cookies vom
                  Browser unterstützt wurden, ansonsten '0'.
&lt;/pre&gt;</t>
</str>

<str id="28">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Enabled</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="29">
<new/>
<o>Log requests</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="30">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Log file</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="31">
<o>The log file. &lt;pre&gt;%y    Year  (e.g. '1997')
%m    Month (e.g. '08')
%d    Date  (e.g. '10' for the tenth)
%h    Hour  (e.g. '00')
%H    Hostname
&lt;/pre&gt;</o>
<t>Ein Dateiname. Einige Ersetzungen werden vorgenommen:
&lt;pre&gt;
%y    Jahr     (z.B. '1997')
%m    Monat    (z.B. '08')
%d    Tag      (z.B. '10' für den 10. des Monats)
%h    Stunden  (z.B. '00')
&lt;/pre&gt;</t>
</str>

<str id="32">
<new/>
<o>Logging: No Logging for</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="33">
<o>Don't log requests from hosts with an IP number which matches any of the patterns in this list. This also affects the access counter log.</o>
<t>Für die folgenden IP-Adressen werden keine Log-Einträge vorgenommen.
Dies hat auch Einfluss auf den Access-Counter.</t>
</str>

<str id="34">
<new/>
<o>Domain</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="35">
<o>The domainname of the server. The domainname is used to generate default URLs, and to generate email addresses.</o>
<t>Der Domainname des Servers, der für die Generierung der
Standard-URLs und Email-Adressen verwendet wird.</t>
</str>

<str id="36">
<new/>
<o>Primary Server URL</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="37">
<o>This is the main server URL, where your start page is located. Please note that you also have to configure the 'URLs' variable.</o>
<t>Dies ist die URL des Haupt-Servers, auf dem die Startseite abgelegt ist.</t>
</str>

<str id="38">
<new/>
<o>URLs</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="39">
<new/>
<o>Bind to these URLs. You can use '*' and '?' to perform globbing (using any of these will default to binding to all IP-numbers on your machine).  The possible protocols are http, fhttp (a faster version of the normal HTTP protocol, but not 100% compatible with all modules) https, ftp, ftps, gopher and tetris.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="40">
<new/>
<o>Internal module resource mountpoint</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="41">
<o>Some modules may want to create links to internal resources. This setting configures an internally handled location that can be used for such purposes.  Simply select a location that you are not likely to use for regular resources.</o>
<t>Einige Module erzeugen Links auf interne Ressourcen. Diese Einstellung
bestimmt eine intern verwandte Position im virtuellen Dateisystem, um
solche Zwecke zu erfüllen.  Es sollte ein Wert benutzt werden, der nicht
durch andere Ressourcen benutzt wird.</t>
</str>

<str id="42">
<new/>
<o>Bandwidth Throttling: Server: Enabled</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="43">
<o>If set, per-server bandwidth throttling will be enabled. It will allow you to limit the total available bandwidth for this Virtual Server.&lt;br /&gt;Bandwidth is assigned using a Token Bucket. The principle under which it works is: for each byte we send we use a token. Tokens are added to a repository at a constant rate. When there's not enough, we can't transmit. When there's too many, they "spill" and are lost.</o>
<t>Wenn gesetzt, wird pro Server eine Bandbreitenbegrenzung aktiviert.
Dadurch kann man die zur Verfügung stehende Bandbreite für diesen
virtuellen Server begrenzen.&lt;br&gt;</t>
</str>

<str id="44">
<new/>
<o>Bandwidth Throttling: Server: Average available bandwidth</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="45">
<o>This is the average bandwidth available to this Virtual Server in bytes/sec (the bucket "fill rate").</o>
<t>Dies ist die durchschnittliche Bandbreite, die für diesen virtuellen Server zur Verfügung steht. (in Bytes/Sekunde).</t>
</str>

<str id="46">
<new/>
<o>Bandwidth Throttling: Server: Bucket Depth</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="47">
<new/>
<o>This is the maximum depth of the bucket. After a long enough period of inactivity, a request will get this many unthrottled bytes of data, before throttling kicks back in.&lt;br&gt;Set equal to the Fill Rate in order not to allow any data bursts. This value determines the length of the time over which the bandwidth is averaged.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="48">
<new/>
<o>Bandwidth Throttling: Server: Minimum Grant</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="49">
<new/>
<o>When the bandwidth availability is below this value, connections will be delayed rather than granted minimal amounts of bandwidth. The purpose is to avoid sending too small packets (which would increase the IP overhead).</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="50">
<new/>
<o>Bandwidth Throttling: Server: Maximum Grant</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="51">
<new/>
<o>This is the maximum number of bytes assigned in a single request to a connection. Keeping this number low will share bandwidth more evenly among the pending connections, but keeping it too low will increase IP overhead and (marginally) CPU usage. You'll want to set it just a tiny bit lower than any integer multiple of your network's MTU (typically 1500 for ethernet).</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="52">
<new/>
<o>Bandwidth Throttling: Request: Enabled</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="53">
<new/>
<o>If set, per-request bandwidth throttling will be enabled.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="54">
<new/>
<o>Bandwidth Throttling: Request: Minimum guarranteed bandwidth</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="55">
<new/>
<o>The maximum bandwidth each connection (in bytes/sec) can use is determined combining a number of modules. But doing so can lead to too small or even negative bandwidths for particularly unlucky requests. This variable guarantees a minimum bandwidth for each request.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="56">
<new/>
<o>Bandwidth Throttling: Request: Bucket Depth Multiplier</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="57">
<new/>
<o>The average bandwidth available for each request will be determined by the modules combination. The bucket depth will be determined multiplying the rate by this factor.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="58">
<new/>
<o>Messages: No such file</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="59">
<o>What to return when there is no resource or file available at a certain location.</o>
<t>Dieser Text wird angezeigt, wenn eine nicht verfügbare Datei
aufgerufen wird. '$File' wird ersetzt durch den Dateinamen,
'$Me' durch die Server-URL.</t>
</str>

<str id="60">
<new/>
<o>Welcome text</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="61">
<new/>
<o>The text shown to the user on connect</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="62">
<new/>
<o>User session limit</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="63">
<new/>
<o>The maximum number of times a user can connect at once. 0 means unlimited.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="64">
<new/>
<o>Allow named ftp</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="65">
<new/>
<o>If yes, non-anonymous users can connect</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="66">
<new/>
<o>Allow login with incorrect password/user</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="67">
<new/>
<o>If yes, users can connect with the wrong password and/or username. This is useful since things like .htaccess files can later on authenticate the user.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="68">
<new/>
<o>Allow anonymous ftp</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="69">
<new/>
<o>If yes, anonymous users is allowed to connect.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="70">
<new/>
<o>Shell database</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="71">
<new/>
<o>If this string is set to anything but the empty string, it should point to a file containing a list of valid shells. Users with shells that does not figure in this list will not be allowed to log in.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="72">
<new/>
<o>Show internal errors</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="73">
<o>Show 'Internal server error' messages to the user. This is very useful if you are debugging your own modules or writing Pike scripts.</o>
<t>Anzeige von internen Server-Fehlern an den Benutzer.
Dies ist bei der Entwicklung und bei der Fehlersuche von eigenen Modulen
oder Pike-Scripten nützlich.</t>
</str>

<str id="74">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Set unique user id cookies</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="75">
<o>If set to Yes, all users of your server whose clients support cookies will get a unique 'user-id-cookie', this can then be used in the log and in scripts to track individual users.</o>
<t>An alle Benutzer der Website wird ein eindeutiger Benutzer-Cookie geschickt,
sofern deren Browser Cookies annimmt.  Dieser kann in Scripten und im Logfile
zur Identifizierung einzelner Benutzer verwendet werden.</t>
</str>

<str id="76">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Set ID cookies only once</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="77">
<o>If set to Yes, Roxen will attempt to set unique user ID cookies only upon receiving the first request (and again after some minutes). Thus, if the user doesn't allow the cookie to be set, she won't be bothered with multiple requests.</o>
<t>Dem Benutzer wird nur beim ersten Aufruf ein eindeutiger Benutzer-Cookie
geschickt. Dadurch wird der Benutzer nur einmal aufgefordert, einen Cookie
anzunehmen.</t>
</str>

<str id="78">
<new/>
<o>Logging method</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="79">
<o>None - No log&lt;br /&gt;CommonLog - A common log in a file&lt;br /&gt;Compat - Log through Roxen's normal logging format.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please note that compat limits Roxen to less than 1k requests/second.&lt;/p&gt;</o>
<t>Keine - Kein Logfile&lt;br /&gt;CommonLog - Logging nach dem CommonLog-Format&lt;br /&gt;Compat - Mit Roxen's normalem Format arbeiten.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hinweis: Die Compat-Methode beschränkt Roxen auf 1000 Zugriffe/Sekunde.</t>
</str>

<str id="80">
<new/>
<o>Log file</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="81">
<o>This file is used if logging is done using the CommonLog method.</o>
<t>Logdatei</t>
</str>

<str id="82">
<new/>
<o>Ram cache</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="83">
<o>The size of the ram cache, in MegaBytes</o>
<t>Speicher-Cache</t>
</str>

<str id="84">
<new/>
<o>Client timeout</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="85">
<new/>
<o>The maximum time Roxen will wait for a client before giving up, and close the connection, in seconds</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="86">
<new/>
<o>SSL certificate file</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="87">
<o>The SSL certificate file to use. The path is relative to %s</o>
<t>SSL-Zertifikatsdatei. Der Pfad ist relativ zu %s</t>
</str>

<str id="88">
<new/>
<o>SSL key file</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="89">
<o>The SSL key file to use. The path is relative to %s, you do not have to specify a key file, leave this field empty to use the certificate file only</o>
<t>Die SSL-Schlüsseldatei, die verwendet werden soll. Der Pfad ist relativ zu %s. Die Schlüsseldatei muß nicht angeben werden, sondern man kann dieses Feld leer lassen und nur mit der Zertifikatsdatei arbeiten</t>
</str>

<str id="90">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Log entire file length in restored connections</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="91">
<o>If this toggle is enabled log entries for restored connections will log the amount of sent data plus the restoration location. Ie if a user has downloaded 100 bytes of a file already, and makes a Range request fetching the remaining 900 bytes, the log entry will log it as if the entire 1000 bytes were downloaded. &lt;p&gt;This is useful if you want to know if downloads were successful (the user has the complete file downloaded). The drawback is that bandwidth statistics on the log file will be incorrect. The statistics in Roxen will continue being correct.</o>
<t>Bei wiederaufgenommenen Verbindungen werden die übertragenen Daten sowie die bisher verschickten Daten verzeichnet.  Wenn ein Benutzer bereits 100 Bytes einer Datei geladen hat, und in einem späteren Download die fehlenden 900 Bytes überträgt, werden im Logfile die gesamten 1000 Bytes verzeichnet.&lt;p&gt;Dies ist nützlich, um erfolgreiche Downloads zu erkennen.</t>
</str>

<str id="92">
<new/>
<o>Default font</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="93">
<o>The default font to use when modules request a font.</o>
<t>Die Schriftart, die von Modulen benutzt werden soll.</t>
</str>

<str id="94">
<new/>
<o>Font directories</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="95">
<o>This is where the fonts are located.</o>
<t>In diesen Verzeichnissen befinden sich Schriftarten.</t>
</str>

<str id="96">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Log directory prefix</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="97">
<o>This is the default file path that will be prepended to the log file path in all the default modules and the virtual server.</o>
<t>Alle Logdateien werden unterhalb dieses Verzeichnisses abgelegt.</t>
</str>

<str id="98">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Enabled</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="99">
<o>If set to Yes, caching will be enabled.</o>
<t>Der Proxy-Festplatten-Cache wird benutzt.</t>
</str>

<str id="100">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Clean size</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="101">
<o>Minimum number of Megabytes removed when a garbage collect is done.</o>
<t>Wird der Cache geleert, werden mindestens soviel Megabytes entfernt.</t>
</str>

<str id="102">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Minimum available free space and inodes (in %)</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="103">
<o>If less than this amount of disk space or inodes (in %) is left, the cache will remove a few files. This check may work half-hearted if the diskcache is spread over several filesystems.</o>
<t>Bei Unterschreiten dieses Wertes (in %) werden einige Dateien aus dem Cache entfernt.</t>
</str>

<str id="104">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Size</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="105">
<o>How many MB may the cache grow to before a garbage collect is done?</o>
<t>Maximale Größe des Proxy-Caches auf der Festplatte, in MB.</t>
</str>

<str id="106">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Maximum number of files</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="107">
<o>How many cache files (inodes) may be on disk before a garbage collect is done ? May be left zero to disable this check.</o>
<t>Wie viele Dateien dürfen im Cache sein, bevor eine Reinigung (Garbage Collection) stattfindet. Durch Setzen auf Null wird diese Abfrage ignoriert.</t>
</str>

<str id="108">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache bytes per second</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="109">
<o>How file size should be treated during garbage collect. Each X bytes counts as a second, so that larger files will be removed first.</o>
<t>Wie wichtig ist die Dateigröße beim Reinigen des Caches? Jedes Byte entspricht einem gewissen Dateialter in Sekunden. Größere Dateien werden also eher entfernt.</t>
</str>

<str id="110">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Base Cache Dir</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="111">
<o>This is the base directory where cached files will reside. To avoid mishaps, 'roxen_cache/' is always prepended to this variable.</o>
<t>In diesem Verzeichnis werden die Cache-Dateien abgelegt. Um Pannen zu vermeiden, wird 'roxen_cache' an diesen Wert angehängt.</t>
</str>

<str id="112">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Number of hash directories</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="113">
<o>This is the number of directories to hash the contents of the disk cache into.  Changing this value currently invalidates the whole cache, since the cache cannot find the old files.  In the future, the cache will be recalculated when this value is changed.</o>
<t>Dies ist die Anzahl an Verzeichnissen, auf die die Cache-Dateien verteilt werden.  Das Ändern dieses Wertes macht den bisherigen Proxy-Cache ungültig.</t>
</str>

<str id="114">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Keep without Content-Length</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="115">
<o>Keep files without Content-Length header information in the cache?</o>
<t>Sollen Dateien ohne Content-Length im Cache behalten werden?</t>
</str>

<str id="116">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Refreshes on Last-Modified</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="117">
<o>If set, refreshes files without Expire header information when they have reached double the age they had when they got cached. This may be useful for some regularly updated docs as online newspapers.</o>
<t>Der Cache wird anhand der Last-Modified-Information Dateien aus dem Cache
entfernen, sofern kein Expire-Header vorhanden ist.  Die Dateien verbleiben
im Cache, bis sie ihr Alter verdoppelt haben.</t>
</str>

<str id="118">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Last resort (in days)</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="119">
<o>How many days shall files without Expires and without Last-Modified header information be kept?</o>
<t>Wieviel Tage sollen Dateien ohne Expire- und Last-Modifier-Informationen im Cache verbleiben?</t>
</str>

<str id="120">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Proxy Disk Cache Garbage collector logfile</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="121">
<o>Information about garbage collector runs, removed and refreshed files, cache and disk status goes here.</o>
<t>Informationen über Aktivitäten der Garbage Collection: gelöschte und aktualisierte Dateien, Cache- und Festplatten-Status werden vermerkt.</t>
</str>

<str id="122">
<new/>
<o>PID file</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="123">
<o>In this file, the server will write out it's PID, and the PID of the start script. $pid will be replaced with the pid, and $uid with the uid of the user running the process.
&lt;br /&gt;Note: It can be overridden by the command line option.</o>
<t>In dieser Datei legt der Server seine eigene PID und die des start-Scripts ablegen. $pid wird mit der PID ersetzt und $uid mit der UID des ausführenden Benutzers.</t>
</str>

<str id="124">
<new/>
<o>Identify, Use default identification string</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="125">
<o>Setting this variable to No will display the "Identify as" node where you can state what Roxen should call itself when talking to clients.&lt;br /&gt;It is possible to disable this so that you can enter an identification-string that does not include the actual version of Roxen, as recommended by the HTTP/1.0 draft 03:&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: Revealing the specific software version of the server may allow the server machine to become more vulnerable to attacks against software that is known to contain security holes. Server implementors are encouraged to make this field a configurable option.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</o>
<t>Bei Nein, kann eine andere Identität als der Standardwert eingetragen werden.</t>
</str>

<str id="126">
<new/>
<o>Identify, Identify as</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="127">
<o>Enter the name that Roxen should use when talking to clients. </o>
<t>Hier kann der Namen eingegeben werden, mit dem Roxen sich zu erkennen gibt, wenn ein Client Anfragen stellt.</t>
</str>

<str id="128">
<new/>
<o>Change uid and gid to</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="129">
<o>When roxen is run as root, to be able to open port 80 for listening, change to this user-id and group-id when the port has been opened. If you specify a symbolic username, the default group of that user will be used. The syntax is user[:group].</o>
<t>Wenn Roxen unter der root-Kennung läuft, um den Port 80 
öffnen zu können, wird die User-ID und die Group-ID auf diesen Wert
gesetzt, nachdem der Port geöffnet wurde. Wenn ein Benutzername (z.B. 'www')
verwendet wird, wird die Standardgruppe dieses Benutzers verwendet.
Die Syntax ist user[:group].</t>
</str>

<str id="130">
<new/>
<o>Change uid and gid permanently</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="131">
<o>If this variable is set, roxen will set it's uid and gid permanently. This disables the 'exec script as user' fetures for CGI, and also access files as user in the filesystems, but it gives better security.</o>
<t>Wenn diese Variable gesetzt ist, wird Roxen seine UID und GID permanent
auf die eingestellten Werte wechseln.  Dadurch können CGI-Scripte nicht
mehr unter der Kennung anderer Benutzer ausgeführt werden. Allerdings
erhöht sich so die Sicherheit des Servers.</t>
</str>

<str id="132">
<new/>
<o>Module directories</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="133">
<o>This is a list of directories where Roxen should look for modules. Can be relative paths, from the directory you started Roxen. The directories are searched in order for modules.</o>
<t>Eine Liste von Verzeichnissen, in denen Roxen nach Modulen
suchen wird. Dies können relative Pfade sein.
Die Verzeichnisse werden in der eingegeben Reihenfolge nach Modulen
durchsucht.</t>
</str>

<str id="134">
<new/>
<o>Client supports regexps</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="135">
<o>What do the different clients support?
&lt;br /&gt;The default information is normally fetched from the file server/etc/supports in your Roxen directory.</o>
<t>Welche unterschiedlichen Möglichkeiten werden durch die verschiedenen
Webbrowser unterstützt. Die Standard-Informationen werden aus der
Datei server/etc/supports entnommen, das Format ist:&lt;pre&gt;
Regulärer Ausdruck    Funktion, Funktion
Regulärer Ausdruck    Funktion, Funktion
...
&lt;/pre&gt;Wenn '-' der Funktion vorangestellt wird, wird es von der Liste
entfernt.</t>
</str>

<str id="136">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Audit trail</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="137">
<o>If Audit trail is set to Yes, all changes of uid will be logged in the Event log.</o>
<t>Wenn auf Ja gesetzt, werden sämtliche Wechsel von Benutzerkennungen
im Ereignis-Log verzeichnet.</t>
</str>

<str id="138">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Logging method</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="139">
<o>What method to use for logging, default is file, but syslog is also available. When using file, the output is really sent to stdout and stderr, but this is handled by the start script.</o>
<t>Welche Methode soll für das Logging benutzt werden. Standard ist Datei,
aber Syslog ist ebenfalls möglich.</t>
</str>

<str id="140">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Log PID</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="141">
<o>If set, the PID will be included in the syslog.</o>
<t>Soll Roxen die eigene PID ins Syslog schreiben?</t>
</str>

<str id="142">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Log to system console</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="143">
<o>If set and syslog is used, the error/debug message will be printed to the system console as well as to the system log.</o>
<t>Soll Roxen auf die Konsole schreiben?  Fehler- und Debug-Meldungen werden sowohl auf die Konsole als auch in das Syslog geschrieben.</t>
</str>

<str id="144">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Syslog type</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="145">
<o>When using SYSLOG, which log type should be used.</o>
<t>Wenn Syslog verwendet wird, welcher Typ soll benutzt werden?</t>
</str>

<str id="146">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Log what to syslog</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="147">
<o>When syslog is used, how much should be sent to it?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;Fatal:    Only messages about fatal errors&lt;br /&gt;Errors:   Only error or fatal messages&lt;br /&gt;Warning:  Warning messages as well&lt;br /&gt;Debug:    Debug messager as well&lt;br /&gt;All:      Everything&lt;br /&gt;</o>
<t>Wenn Syslog verwendet wird, welche Informationen sollen festgehalten werden?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;Fatal:    Nur Mitteilungen über fatale Fehler&lt;br /&gt;
          Errors:   Nur Fehler und fatale Mitteilungen&lt;br /&gt;
          Warning:  wie oben, jedoch auch Warnungen&lt;br /&gt;
          Debug:    wie oben, jedoch auch Hinweise&lt;br /&gt;
          All:      Alles&lt;br /&gt;
</t>
</str>

<str id="148">
<new/>
<o>Logging: Log as</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="149">
<o>When syslog is used, this will be the identification of the Roxen daemon. The entered value will be appended to all logs.</o>
<t>Wenn Syslog benutzt wird, wird dieser Wert als Identifikation in allen
Logs angehängt.</t>
</str>

<str id="150">
<new/>
<o>Number of threads to run</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="151">
<o>The number of simultaneous threads Roxen will use.
&lt;p&gt;Please note that even if this is one, Roxen will still be able to serve multiple requests, using a select loop based system.
&lt;i&gt;This is quite useful if you have more than one CPU in your machine, or if you have a lot of slow NFS accesses.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</o>
<t>Die Anzahl an parallelen Threads, mit denen Roxen arbeiten wird.\n
Hinweis: Auch wenn nur ein Thread eingestellt wird, können mehrere
Zugriffe gleichzeitig bearbeitet werden.\n
&lt;i&gt;Dies ist nützlich für Mehrprozessor-Systeme.&lt;/i&gt;</t>
</str>

<str id="152">
<new/>
<o>Update the supports database automatically</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="153">
<o>If set to Yes, the etc/supports file will be updated automatically from www.roxen.com now and then. This is recomended, since you will then automatically get supports information for new clients, and new versions of old ones.</o>
<t>Die Datei /etc/supports wird automatisch von www.roxen.com aktualisiert.
Dadurch erhält man immer die aktuelle Liste aller bekannten Features.</t>
</str>

<str id="154">
<new/>
<o>ABS: Enable Anti-Block-System</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="155">
<o>If set, the anti-block-system will be enabled. This will restart the server after a configurable number of minutes if it locks up. If you are running in a single threaded environment heavy calculations will also halt the server. In multi-threaded mode bugs such as eternal loops will not cause the server to reboot, since only one thread is blocked. In general there is no harm in having this option enabled. </o>
<t>Das AntiBlockSystem wird aktiviert, dies startet den Server nach einer
einstellbaren Zahl von Minuten neu, wenn ein Thread blockiert ist.  Bei
mehr als einem Thread wird der gesamte Server nicht komplett angehalten,
sondern nur der blockierte Thread.  Im allgemeinen hat diese Option keine
Nachteile.</t>
</str>

<str id="156">
<new/>
<o>ABS: Timeout</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="157">
<o>If the server is unable to accept connection for this many minutes, it will be restarted. You need to find a balance: if set too low, the server will be restarted even if it's doing legal things (like generating many images), if set too high you might get a long downtime if the server for some reason locks up.</o>
<t>Wenn der Server soviele Minuten nicht in der Lage ist, Anfragen
zu beantworten, wird er neu gestartet.  Zu beachten ist, daß
bei komplexen Berechnungen es durchaus normal ist, wenn eine
Anfrage eine Weile benötigt.</t>
</str>

<str id="158">
<new/>
<o>Default language</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="159">
<o>Locale, used to localize all messages in Roxen.
Standard means using the default locale, which varies according to the value of the 'LANG' environment variable.</o>
<t>Die Sprache, in der alle Roxen-Meldungen ausgeben werden.
'standard' ist abhängig von der LANG Umgebungsvariable.</t>
</str>

<str id="160">
<new/>
<o>Auto Restart: Enable Automatic Restart</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="161">
<o>If set, Roxen will automatically restart after a configurable number of days. Since Roxen uses a monolith, non-forking server model the process tends to grow in size over time. This is mainly due to heap fragmentation but also because of memory leaks.</o>
<t>Wenn gesetzt, wird Roxen automatisch nach einer bestimmten Anzahl von
Tagen neugestartet. Hin und wieder wächst der Roxen-Prozess im Laufe der
Zeit an. Diese Option ist in diesem Falle dann sinnvoll.</t>
</str>

<str id="162">
<new/>
<o>Auto Restart: Timeout</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="163">
<o>Automatically restart the server after this many days.</o>
<t>Roxen wird nach soviel Tagen automatisch neugestartet.</t>
</str>

<str id="164">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Store the argument cache in a mysql database</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="165">
<o>If set, store the argument cache in a mysql database. This is very useful for load balancing using multiple Roxen servers, since the mysql database will handle synchronization.</o>
<t>Wenn gesetzt, wird der Argumenten-Cache in eine SQL-Datenbank gespeichert. Dies ist sinnvoll bei mehreren Roxen-Servern, da die Datenbank die Synchronisation übernimmt.</t>
</str>

<str id="166">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Argument Cache Database URL to use</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="167">
<o>The database to use to store the argument cache.</o>
<t>Welche Datenbank soll für den Argumenten-Cache benutzt werden?</t>
</str>

<str id="168">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Argument Cache Directory</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="169">
<o>The cache directory to use to store the argument cache. Please note that load balancing is not available for most modules  (such as gtext, diagram etc) unless you use a mysql database to store the argument cache meta data.</o>
<t>Dieses Verzeichnis wird für die Speicherung des Argumenten-Caches benutzt.  Für Load-Balancing sollte jedoch eine SQL-Datenbank verwendet werden.</t>
</str>

<str id="170">
<new/>
<o>Cache: Memory Cache Garbage Collect Interval</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="171">
<o>The number of seconds between every garbage collect (removal of old content) from the memory cache. The memory cache is used for various tasks like remebering what supports flags matches what client.</o>
<t>Wieviele Sekunden sollen zwischen zwei Ausführungen einer Garbage Collection im Speicher-Cache liegen? Der Speicher-Cache enthält u.a. die Supports-Daten.</t>
</str>

<str id="172">
<new/>
<o>Commented config files</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="173">
<new/>
<o>Save the variable documentation strings as comments in the configuration files. Only useful if you read or edit the config files directly.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="174">
<new/>
<o>Show documentation</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="175">
<new/>
<o>Show the variable documentation.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="176">
<new/>
<o>Show advanced configuration options</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="177">
<new/>
<o>Show all possible configuration options, not only the ones that are most often changed.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="178">
<new/>
<o>Show the incomplete translations</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="179">
<new/>
<o>Show the language selection flags. The translation of the configuration interface is not done yet, so this is mostly useful for the curious or the translator.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="180">
<new/>
<o>Show developer options and actions</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="181">
<new/>
<o>Show settings and actions that are not normaly useful for non-developer users. If you develop your own roxen modules, this option is for you.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="182">
<new/>
<o>Background color</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="183">
<new/>
<o>Administration interface background color.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="184">
<new/>
<o>Text color</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="185">
<new/>
<o>Administration interface text color.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="186">
<new/>
<o>Link color</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="187">
<new/>
<o>Font</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="188">
<new/>
<o>Administration interface font.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="189">
<new/>
<o>Add/Delete module page type</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="190">
<new/>
<o>&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;normal&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Show module name and documentation with images.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;fast&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Like normal, but no type images.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;faster&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Like normal, but allows to select multiple modules at once.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;compact&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Only show the names of modules, and allow addition/deletion of multiple modules at once.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;really compact&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Like compact, but no module classes.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="191">
<new/>
<o>All Permissions</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="192">
<new/>
<o>View Settings</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="193">
<new/>
<o>Edit Users</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="194">
<new/>
<o>Edit Global Variables</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="195">
<new/>
<o>Edit Module Variables</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="196">
<o>Tasks</o>
<t>Aufgaben</t>
</str>

<str id="197">
<o>Restart</o>
<t>Neustart</t>
</str>

<str id="198">
<o>Shutdown</o>
<t>Anhalten</t>
</str>

<str id="199">
<new/>
<o>Create Sites</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="200">
<new/>
<o>Add Modules</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="bA">
<o>Save</o>
<t>Sichern</t>
</str>

<str id="201">
<o>Ok</o>
<t>OK</t>
</str>

<str id="202">
<o>Cancel</o>
<t>Abbruch</t>
</str>

<str id="203">
<o>Next</o>
<t>Weiter</t>
</str>

<str id="204">
<o>Administration Interface</o>
<t>Administrations-Interface</t>
</str>

<str id="205">
<o>Language</o>
<t>Sprache</t>
</str>

<str id="206">
<new/>
<o>User</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="cw">
<o>and</o>
<t>und</t>
</str>

<str id="207">
<o>every</o>
<t>jede</t>
</str>

<str id="208">
<o>since</o>
<t>seit</t>
</str>

<str id="209">
<o>Notice</o>
<t>Notiz</t>
</str>

<str id="210">
<o>Warning</o>
<t>Warnung</t>
</str>

<str id="211">
<o>Error</o>
<t>Fehler</t>
</str>

<str id="212">
<new/>
<o>Admin</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="213">
<o>Sites</o>
<t>Sites</t>
</str>

<str id="214">
<o>Globals</o>
<t>Globale Einstellungen</t>
</str>

<str id="215">
<o>Ports</o>
<t>Ports</t>
</str>

<str id="216">
<o>Events</o>
<t>Ereignis-Log</t>
</str>

<str id="217">
<new/>
<o>Docs</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="218">
<o>Startpage</o>
<t>Startseite</t>
</str>

<str id="219">
<new/>
<o>Update</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="220">
<o>Your Settings</o>
<t>Benutzer-Einstellungen</t>
</str>

<str id="221">
<o>Users</o>
<t>Benutzer</t>
</str>

<str id="222">
<o>Create new user</o>
<t>Neuen Benutzer anlegen</t>
</str>

<str id="223">
<o>Delete old user</o>
<t>Bestehenden Benutzer löschen</t>
</str>

<str id="224">
<new/>
<o>Create User</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="225">
<new/>
<o>User ID</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="226">
<o>Permission denied</o>
<t>Erlaubnis verweigert</t>
</str>

<str id="227">
<o>Delete</o>
<t>Löschen</t>
</str>

<str id="228">
<new/>
<o>Status</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="229">
<o>Maintenance</o>
<t>Pflege</t>
</str>

<str id="230">
<new/>
<o>SSL</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="231">
<o>Debug information</o>
<t>Debug-Informationen</t>
</str>

<str id="232">
<o>All memory caches have been flushed.</o>
<t>Alle Speicher-Caches wurden geleert.</t>
</str>

<str id="233">
<new/>
<o>Roxen will restart automatically.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="234">
<new/>
<o>You might see the old process for a while in the process table
when doing 'ps' or running 'top'. This is normal. Roxen waits for a
while for all connections to finish, the process will go away after at
most 15 minutes.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="235">
<new/>
<o>Roxen will &lt;b&gt;not&lt;/b&gt; restart automatically.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="dH">
<new/>
<o>Not available.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="dI">
<new/>
<o>All available fonts</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="236">
<new/>
<o>Example text</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="237">
<new/>
<o>Jackdaws love my big sphinx of quartz.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="238">
<o>Features</o>
<t>Features</t>
</str>

<str id="dM">
<o>Disabled modules</o>
<t>Deaktivierte Module</t>
</str>

<str id="239">
<o>All modules</o>
<t>Alle Module</t>
</str>

<str id="240">
<new/>
<o>Name</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="241">
<new/>
<o>State</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="242">
<o>Disabled</o>
<t>Deaktiviert</t>
</str>

<str id="243">
<o>N/A</o>
<t>N/A</t>
</str>

<str id="244">
<o>Enabled</o>
<t>Aktiviert</t>
</str>

<str id="245">
<o>Normal</o>
<t>Normal</t>
</str>

<str id="246">
<o>Reversed</o>
<t>Umgekehrt</t>
</str>

<str id="247">
<o>Clear Log</o>
<t>Log löschen</t>
</str>

<str id="248">
<o>Create new site</o>
<t>Neue Site anlegen</t>
</str>

<str id="249">
<new/>
<o>Drop old site</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="250">
<o>Empty</o>
<t>Leer</t>
</str>

<str id="400">
<new/>
<o>Initial Variables</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="255">
<new/>
<o>Disabling old configuration %s
</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="256">
<o>Settings</o>
<t>Einstellungen</t>
</str>

<str id="257">
<o>Modules</o>
<t>Module</t>
</str>

<str id="258">
<new/>
<o>Add module</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="259">
<new/>
<o>Drop module</o>
<t></t>
</str>


<pike>

string full_status(string real_version, int boot_time,
     		   int days, int hrs, int min, int sec, string sent_data,
		   float kbps, string sent_headers, int num_requests,
		   float rpm, string received_data) {
  return(sprintf("<table>"
		 "<tr><td><b>Version:</b></td><td colspan=\"2\">%s</td></tr>\n"
		 "<tr><td><b>Booted on:</b></td><td colspan=\"2\">%s</td></tr>\n"
		 "<tr><td><b>Uptime:</b></td>"
		 "<td colspan=\"2\">%d day%s, %02d:%02d:%02d</td></tr>\n"
		 "<tr><td colspan=\"3\">&nbsp;</td></tr>\n"
		 "<tr><td><b>Sent data:</b></td><td>%s"
		 "</td><td>%.2f Kbit/sec</td></tr><tr>\n"
		 "<td><b>Sent headers:</b></td><td>%s</td></tr>\n"

		 "<tr><td><b>Number of requests:</b></td>"
		 "<td>%8d</td><td>%.2f/min</td></tr>\n"
		 "<tr><td><b>Received data:</b></td>"
		 "<td>%s</td></tr>\n"
		 "</table>",
		 real_version, ctime(boot_time),
		 days, (days==1?"":"s"), hrs, min, sec,
		 sent_data, kbps, sent_headers,
		 num_requests, rpm, received_data));
}

string ftp_stat_line(string cmd, int times) {
  return(sprintf("<tr align=\"right\"><td><b>%s</b></td>"
		 "<td align=\"right\">%d</td><td> time%s</td></tr>\n",
		 cmd, times, (times == 1)?"":"s"));
}

</pike>

<str id="251">
<o>Add Module</o>
<t>Modul hinzuzfügen</t>
</str>

<str id="252">
<o>Drop Module</o>
<t>Modul löschen</t>
</str>

<str id="253">
<o>Reload</o>
<t>Reload</t>
</str>

<str id="254">
<new/>
<o>Module homepage</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="260">
<new/>
<o>Request status</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="261">
<new/>
<o>Inherit tree</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="dt">
<new/>
<o>Administrator logged on as %s from %s.
</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="262">
<new/>
<o>Character encoding</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="263">
<new/>
<o>Send pages to client in this character encoding.</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="264">
<new/>
<o>Mountpoint</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="265">
<new/>
<o>Usually / is a good idea</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="266">
<new/>
<o>Will be loaded from: </o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="267">
<new/>
<o>View</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="268">
<new/>
<o>Configuration gone!</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="269">
<new/>
<o>Site name:</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="270">
<new/>
<o>
The name of the configuration must contain characters
other than space and tab, it should not end with
~, and it must not be 'CVS', 'Global Variables' or
'global variables', nor the name of an existing
configuration, and the character '/' cannot be
used. This name will show up in the sites menu, a
lowercased, filesystem-friendly version will become
the virtual server's configuration file name as well
as the name of its log file directory.
</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="271">
<o>with template</o>
<t>Mit Template</t>
</str>

<str id="272">
<new/>
<o>Reload module list</o>
<t></t>
</str>

<str id="273">
<new/>
<o>Select one or several modules to add.</o>
<t></t>
</str>
